michelefranzesemoda.com 2019-12-02

# Privacy Terms - Michele Franzese Moda

INFO

**Michele Franzese** is the leading fashion retailer in South Italy.

Since 1992, the company is headquartered in St. Anastasia in via Antonio D'Auria where there is today his palace of fashion in the heart of the city  and from 2010 in Naples in Via Domenico Morelli (Piazza dei Martiri) is the most prestigious showcase of Campania.

Since 2015 **Michele Franzese Moda** is on the web with a site that offers collections for men, women and children of the most prestigious fashion designers like Saint Laurent, Valentino, Alexander McQueen, Givenchy, Tom Ford, Dsquared, Balmain Paris, Fausto Puglisi , Maison Margiela, Stone Island, N° 21, Kenzo, Moschino, MSGM and creative avant-garde like Heron Preston, Yeezy, Palm Angels, Off-White and many others. As an authorized dealer of all brands on the site, **MICHELEFRANZESEMODA** guarantees the authenticity of every item.

E-Commerce, Analythics and Social Network

10,000 visitors accessing the site **MICHELEFRANZESEMODA.COM** in early 2015. In the last period, visitors increased by 5 times.

Since 2009 **Michele Franzese** incorporated in its marketing strategy the social networks. **MICHELEFRANZESEMODA.COM** was one of the first companies in Southern Italy who believed and invested in the use of these new communication channels. In the last six years the 74,000 Facebook fans and 34,000 Instagram fans grew up in a community of followers and supporters which now has 110,000 regular contacts. Today Facebook and Instagram are the main platforms of the company that produces the largest number of traffic to the online store.

**MICHELEFRANZESEMODA.COM** is constantly followed and supported by experts in marketing and communication and is therefore also on other social networking sites like Twitter, Youtube, Instagram and Pinterest, continues growing. The staff that follow the website is professional and has qualifications in the field of fashion and design.

**Michele Franzese Magazine** is a new portal for interaction and sharing that provides users with information on the trends of the moment, the Must Have and new designers, with exclusive photos, videos and news, run by a team of creative professionals.

Customer Service

**Packaging**

All orders placed on MICHELEFRANZESEMODA.COM depart from the place of St. Anastasia with the utmost care for the packaging and meticulous attention to details.

**Personal Shopper**

Our Customer Service is available to answer any questions, problems or requests always offering impeccable customer service (E-mail: info@michelefranzesemoda.com, Phone: +39081530 64 93, Whatsapp: +39 393 87 51 105). 

**PURCHASE RETURNS**

Michele Franzese Moda wishes to ensure complete satisfaction to their customers also by offering the opportunity to return one or more ordered items and receive a refund equal to the price of the returned items. The return of the goods are at the expense and under the responsibility of the Customer that will need to act and send an email return request within 72 working hours after delivery date and then only if the goods meet all the “conditions of return” listed below. Michele Franzese Moda have the right to ask for pics to customers of the items wished to be returned. From the authorization approval, the customer must use an express delivery, since the package needs to reach our headquarter within 10 working days. We will not accept the retrieval if this rule will not be respected

**  CONDITIONS OF THE RETURN**

A) - All items for sale on the site Michele Franzese Moda are delivered with an authenticity card attached to the clothing using a disposable safety seal bearing Michele Franzese Moda  logo. The clothing must be tried for size without removing this card and without damaging the seal. Returns will be accepted only with the safety seal perfectly intact, which may be a plastic seal on wire or in the case of some shoes, a label placed on the sole. We will in no case accept returns with the safety seal chipped, broken, disconnected, removed or tampered with.  
B) - The Items that have any sign of use or wear will not be accepted and will be returned to the client.  
C) – The items needs to be returned under the same conditions in which they were shipped to the customer and must be wrapped and packed properly.  
D) - All the other labels of the item, both in tissue or pending, must never be removed from the article.  
E) - The goods to be returned must be handed over within 10 working days from the return authorization  
F) - The customer who wishes to undertake size, colour or item change, must perform “The Return Procedure”, see below,and make a new order on the site Michele Franzese Moda

G) We do not accept returns or changes for every articles that have a Throwing Dates and/or Capsule collections

H) Any defects in the items must be promptly reported within 72 hours of receipt of the order.

In case of failed return, the customer will have to comply with the conditions listed above, Michele Franzese Moda reserves the right not to accept the goods delivered and returned to the client at the expense of the latter.

**RETURN OR EXCHANGE PROCEDURE**

In order to return a received item please follow carefully “the return procedure” that we here describe through the following steps:

A). If an item does not fit or you do not like it, you can return it. Send a return request   **within 72  working hours **from the goods receipt at eshop@michelefranzesemoda.com. Please include Order Number and Code(s) of the item(s)

B). Send the package back to  Via Pomigliano 122, 80048 Sant' Anastasia - Napoli \- Napoli.  The return shipment of goods is at customers full responsibility. The expedition is at the risk of the Customer: Michele Franzese Moda is not responsible for any loss or damage due to inadequate packaging or delay in delivery. The articles must be returned in the same package in which they were received or same type.

C) In the case that a refund is requested, the cost of shipping and any duty fees are the responsability of the Client.

This amount will be deducted from the final refund. If you choose Store Credit instead you will recieve a code which can be used for a new order and in this case the credit corresponds to the full amount of the returned item.

D) In case which the customer recieve defected items, or there will be mistakes in shipping from Michelefranzesemoda.com, is required to follow the instructions written above. Michelefranzesemoda.com have the right to request pictures proof before authorizing returns of defected goods.

E) Swimwear and underwear(bikini, slip, boxers etc.) must be tried above the personal underwear. The return of this items will be rejected and shipped back to the customer in the case the transparent label of hygienic protection has been removed, or in case the items presents signs of use.

F) The authorized returns from Michelefranzesemoda.com, must be shipped from the same origin Nation where the order has been delivered.

G) Michelefranzesemoda.com have moreover the right to reject not authorized returns or that not follows the conditions written.

For all the aspects not specifically expressed, the European regulation for distance trading will take place

For informations call 081 530 64 93  

All items will be made subject to inspection by the **Michele Franzese Moda** staff that will verify compliance with the conditions od return. Michele Franzese Moda reserves the right to assess additional charges if they prove necessary to ensure the resale of the returned items. These amounts will be determined after the evaluation of the condition of the returned items and communicated to the Customer. Return delivery costs will be charged to the client by deduction from the due refund amount

**REIMBURSEMENT**

If the return procedure was performed properly, in compliance with all mentioned conditions, the Customer will receive an email of acceptance of occurred return. The reimbursement will usually happen by redirecting the amount due to the processed credit card (if the case the order was paid by credit card), PayPal account(if the order was paid with PayPal)or wire transfer in the case of bank transfer

                       TERMS & CONDITIONS

Luxury of love srl \- With registered office in Via Domenico Morelli, 6 / B - 80123 Naples holder of the activities available at the site MICHELEFRANZESEMODA.COM, reserves the right to use the personal data, voluntarily provided by users, in accordance with applicable regulations (Articles 13 et seq . Legislative Decree no. 196/2003).

Users are therefore invited to visit this page periodically for updates on changes related to changes in current legislation.

Luxury of love srl It ensures users that their personal data will be reserved for use strictly connected to the provision of their services, facilitation of site management and the execution of orders.  

The data voluntarily provided by users, will in no case disclosed to third parties.  

If paying by credit card, the information essential for the success of the transaction (number of credit card / debit card, expiration date, security code) will be sent to the registration authority of the treatment (in this case, the UniCredit Bank), or possibly a company responsible for controlling fraud by encryption, without third parties in any way have access. This information will never be seen or stored by the Seller (Luxury of love Srl).  

Luxury of love srl take appropriate security measures in order to minimize the risk of destruction or loss of data, unauthorized access or treatment not allowed or inconsistent with the purposes of collection as indicated in our Privacy Policy.

However Luxury of love srl It can not guarantee its users that the measures taken for the safety of the site and the transmission of data and information on the site are able to limit or exclude any risk of unauthorized access or dispersion of data by devices of relevance 'user. For this reason, we advise users of the site to make sure your computer is equipped with appropriate software to protect the network transmission of data (such as updated antivirus) and that your Internet service provider has taken appropriate measures for the security of the transmission of data in the network.

Luxury of love srl It informs that users can exercise their rights under Article 7 of Legislative Decree no. 196/2003, set forth below in its essential part. Users have the right to request a Luxury of love Srl the following information:  

    1- the confirmation of the existence of personal data concerning him2- the clear communication of the data and its source3- the reason and purpose of their existence and their use  

The request for the above information can be renewed with a minimum of 90 days, except in those cases where there is good cause: cancellation or modification of the data in case of violation of the law; erasure of data that are not used for the aims for which they were collected.

**INFORMATION REGARDING THE PROCESSING OF PERSONAL DATA**

pursuant to and for the effects of Art. 13 of the New European Regulation 2016/279 concerning the protection of individuals with regard to the processing of personal data (GENERAL DATA PROTECTION REGULATION - GDPR)

As required by the General Regulation on the Protection of Personal Data of the European Union (GDPR 2016/679, Article 13), before proceeding with processing, the interested party (user of the website www.michelefranzesemoda.com) is informed that personal data collected through the site are processed by the Company through IT and / or telematic tools, for the purposes indicated in this statement.

To this end, the Data Subject is subject to the Privacy Statement prepared by Luxury of love S.r.l. - with registered office in via Domenico Morelli, 6 / B - 80123 Naples, creator and promoter of the activities available on the site www.michelefranzesemoda.com

**HOLDER OF THE TREATMENT**

The Data Controller of personal data is Luxury Of Love S.R.L, with registered office in via Domenico Morelli, 6 / B - 80123 Naples, e-mail: privacy@franzesemoda.it.

For further information regarding the rights of the interested party, please consider the Paragraph entitled "Rights of the interested parties" of this statement.

**Treatment information**

The personal data processed is collected directly by Luxury Of Love S.R.L or by third parties expressly authorized by it, or communicated by the Company to such third parties for the pursuit of the purposes described below.

**Legal basis and purpose of the processing**

The personal data provided by the user when browsing the website www.michelefranzesemoda.com are processed by the Data Controller in accordance with the current regulations on the protection of personal data. The legal basis of the processing is identified in the provision of its services by the Company, in the management and facilitation of the website, as well as in the establishment, execution and possible termination of the on-line sales contract concluded between the parties and in the obligations to the same contract connected and / or directly and / or indirectly deriving from it. The processing of personal data by MICHELE FRANZESE MODA is aimed at the pursuit of the following purposes:

1) REGISTRATION TO THE NEWSLETTER OF MICHELEFRANZESEMODA.COM: in the event that the user decides to subscribe to the "Newsletter of MICHELE FRANZESE MODA", only following a possible and specific consent, the personal data will be processed by the Data Controller sending commercial or promotional communications, updates related, for example, to latest trends, new arrivals, exclusive offers, special events and promotions. To unsubscribe from the newsletter simply click on the unsubscription link at the bottom of the e-mails received or by writing to privacy@franzesemoda.it

2) REGISTRATION ON MICHELEFRANZESEMODA.COM: in the event that the user decides to register on the site michelefranzesemoda.com, only following a possible and specific consent, the personal data will be processed by the Data Controller for the purpose of registration on michelefranzesemoda.com.

In particular, in the face of the conferment of your name, surname, e-mail address and the setting of an access password, these will be processed to create a personal account, to speed up the purchase process, to allow the user to view the status of orders and receive updates on purchases made, change personal settings and update the account, view the history of returns and requests for change of goods, save the favorite items in the Wishlist.

3) ONLINE SHOPPING ACTIVITIES: the personal data provided will be used for the establishment, management, execution and / or conclusion of the on-line sales contract. The data provided will be processed by the Data Controller for the purpose of managing the purchase order with reference, for example, to the activity of payment, shipping, taking charge of any returns, for customer assistance, for the execution of the purposes administrative - accounting related to the management of the order, for the fulfillment of obligations under current legislation. In case of payment by credit card, the fundamental information for the execution of the transaction (credit / debit card number, expiration date, security code) will be processed by Banca Sella - Worldpay - Adyen or, possibly, by companies in charge of the anti-fraud control using an encrypted protocol and without any third parties being able to access it in any way. Such information will never be viewed or stored by the Luxury Of Love S.R.L seller, with registered office in via Domenico Morelli, 6 / B - 80123 Naples.

4) PROFILING OF PHYSICAL PERSON: only following a possible and explicit consent, the personal data provided may be processed by the Data Controller for profiling activities, ie analysis of preferences aimed at creating content and personalized offers.

**Nature of treatment**

In relation to the purposes referred to in point 1) of the previous paragraph, the provision of personal data and consent to their processing is optional. Failure to provide the consent will make it impossible for MICHELE FRANZESE to register for the "MICHELE FRANZESE Newsletter", to send commercial or promotional messages, updates concerning, for example, latest trends, new arrivals, exclusive offers, special events and promotions. If the user decides to proceed to the newsletter subscription through the section of the site solely dedicated to this activity, the provision of personal data and consent to their treatment is mandatory. Failure to provide consent implies the impossibility for MICHELE FRANZESE MODA to allow registration to the "Newsletter of MICHELE FRANZESE", the sending of commercial or promotional communications, updates concerning, for example, the latest trends, new arrivals , exclusive offers, special events and promotions. In relation to the purposes referred to in point 2) of the previous paragraph, the provision of personal data and consent to their processing is mandatory. Failure to provide consent will make it impossible for MICHELE FRANZESE MODA to register on michelefranzesemoda.com, create a personal account, speed up the purchase process, view the status of orders and receive updates on the purchases made, the possibility for the user to change personal settings and update the account, view the history of returns and requests for change of goods, to save the favorite items in the Wishlist.

In relation to the purposes referred to in point 3) of the previous paragraph, the provision of personal data and consent to their processing is mandatory. Failure to provide the consent will make it impossible for MICHELE FRANZESE MODA to proceed with the establishment, management, execution and / or conclusion of the on-line sales contract, therefore the impossibility to perform, by way of example, the activities linked payment, dispatch, taking charge of any returns, customer service activities, the execution of administrative and accounting purposes related to the management of the order, and the fulfillment of obligations under current legislation.

In relation to the purposes referred to in point 4) of the previous paragraph, the provision of personal data and consent to their processing is optional.

Failure to provide the consent will make it impossible for MICHELE FRANZESE MODA to carry out profiling activities, or to carry out analyzes of preferences aimed at creating personalized contents and offers

**Personal data processed**

The personal data processed by the Data Controller are those provided by the user when browsing the website www.michelefranzesemoda.com, on the occasion of any registration / subscription to the services / programs made available to MICHELE FRANZESE MODA and / or any purchase of products made available to MICHELE FRANZESE MODA, such as, for example: name, surname and e-mail address, in addition to the data required for the provision of the online sales service such as, for example, the functional ones to the execution of the payment and to the shipment / exchange of the purchased products.

**Methods of Processing and Storage of Data**

The processing of personal data is performed by the Owner in compliance with the provisions of the current legislation on Privacy. The Data Controller processes personal data using IT and / or telematic tools and with organizational and logical procedures strictly related to the pursuit of the purposes indicated in this statement, as well as adopting the appropriate security measures to prevent access, disclosure, unauthorized modification or destruction of personal data, their loss and their illicit and incorrect use. However, the Company can not guarantee its users that the measures taken for site security and the transmission of data and information on the site are capable of limiting or excluding any risk of unauthorized access or loss of data by devices pertaining to the user. For this reason, it is suggested to users of the site to make sure that their computer is equipped with appropriate software to protect the transmission of data (for example, updated antivirus) and that its Internet Provider has adopted appropriate measures for the security of transmission of data on the network. The Company also undertakes to process the data according to the principles of correctness, lawfulness and transparency, to collect them to the extent necessary and exact for processing and to allow their use only by personnel for the authorized purpose. The management and storage of personal data acquired will take place in archives or on servers located within the European Union owned by the Owner and / or by third-party companies appointed External Responsible for processing and, in any case, currently located in Italy.

In relation to the different purposes for which they are collected, personal data will be kept for the time strictly necessary to achieve them and, in any case, in accordance with the relevant regulations in force.

In any case, the Company will take care to avoid the use of data indefinitely by proceeding, on a regular basis, to verify appropriately the effective permanence of the interest of the subject to which they refer.

**Recipients and Managers of the treatment**

The data collected will not be disseminated in any way, but will be treated within the limits and for the purposes described by the employees of the Company on the basis of adequate operating instructions (for example, administrative, commercial, marketing, legal, system administrators, etc .). Some data processing may also be performed by third parties, appointed External Responsible for Processing, of which the Data Controller relies on or could be used in the management of the contractual relationship, the provision of services offered and organizational needs of its activities. In particular, the data could be communicated to:

a) subjects, public and private, that can access the data by virtue of the provision of law, regulation or community legislation, within the limits set by these rules;

b) subjects who need access to data for purposes related to the contractual relationship existing between the parties, within the limits strictly necessary for the performance of auxiliary tasks (such as, for example, banks and lenders, technical service providers, hosting providers, IT companies, communication agencies, mail carriers and shipping companies);

c) consultants, within the limits necessary for carrying out their professional duties.

The updated list of External Managers and persons authorized to process the data is kept at the Data Controller's registered office and is available to the interested party, following a request by e-mail to the address privacy@franzesemoda.it

**Data transfer abroad**

The management and storage of personal data will be carried out on servers of the Owner and / or third-party companies duly appointed as External Data Processors located within the European Union.

Personal data may be transferred abroad, in accordance with the provisions of current legislation, even in countries outside the European Union. The transfer to countries outside the EU, in addition to cases in which this is guaranteed by Commission Decisions of Adequacy, is carried out in such a way as to provide appropriate and appropriate guarantees pursuant to art. 46 or 47 or 49 of the Rules.

**Interested Rights**

As an interested party, the user may exercise, at any time, the rights provided for in articles 15, 16, 17, 18, 20 and 21 of the GDPR which, in particular, confer the right to:

a) obtain from the Data Controller, pursuant to Article 15, confirmation that a personal data processing is being processed and, in this case, obtain access to the data and information such as: (i) the purposes of the processing; (ii) the categories of personal data; (iii) the recipients or categories of recipients to whom the personal data have been or will be communicated, in particular if they are recipients located in Third Countries or International Organizations; (iv) when possible, the retention period of the personal data provided or, if not possible, the criteria used to determine this period;

b) obtain from the Data Controller, pursuant to Article 16, the correction of inaccurate personal data concerning him without undue delay; taking into account the purposes of the processing, the data subject has the right to obtain the integration of incomplete personal data, also by providing an additional declaration;

c) obtain from the Data Controller, pursuant to Article 17, the deletion of personal data concerning him without undue delay. The Owner has the obligation to cancel, without undue delay, personal data if there is one of the reasons indicated in paragraph 1 of Article 17;

d) obtain from the Data Controller, pursuant to Art. 18, the limitation of treatment when one of the hypotheses governed by paragraph 1 of Article 18 occurs;

e) obtain from the Data Controller, pursuant to Article 20, the portability of data or receive in a structured format, in common use and readable by an automatic device, the personal data concerning him provided to a Data Controller. The Data Subject also has the right to transmit such data to another Data Controller without impediments by the first Data Controller to whom it has provided them, if the conditions indicated in Article 20 paragraph 1 are met. Finally, the Data Subject has the right to obtain the direct transmission of personal data from one Data Controller to another, if technically feasible;

f) object, in whole or in part, pursuant to Article 21, to the processing of personal data concerning him.

To exercise their rights, the user can send their requests to privacy@franzesemoda.it

It should also be noted that the Data Subject has the right to revoke the consent at any time without prejudice to the lawfulness of the treatment based on the consent given prior to the revocation, without prejudice to the consequences indicated above regarding a refusal to provide such personal data . The Data Subject also has the right to lodge a complaint with a Control Authority.

You can make requests regarding the exercise of these rights by contacting the Data Controller at the e-mail address privacy@fanzesemoda.it Luxury Of Love S.R.L undertakes to respond to the requests of the interested party within a period of one month, except in cases of particular complexity for which it could take up to a maximum of three months. In any case, the Data Controller will provide the interested party with the reason for waiting within one month of the request. The outcome of the request will be provided in writing or in electronic format. In case of request for rectification, cancellation and limitation of processing, the Data Controller undertakes to communicate the results of the requests received by the Data Subject to each of the recipients of his data, unless this proves impossible or involves a disproportionate effort. The Company specifies that a contribution may be requested from the Interested Party if the applications are manifestly unfounded, excessive or repetitive; in this regard, the Data Controller will provide a register to track the requests for intervention. Changes to this information The data controller reserves the right to make changes to this Privacy Policy at any time by giving notice to users on the website www.michelefranzesemoda.com. Therefore, please consult this page often, referring to the date of last modification indicated at the end of the document. In case of non-acceptance of the changes made to this Privacy Policy, the Data Subject may request the Data Controller to delete their personal data. Unless otherwise specified, the previous Privacy Policy will continue to apply to personal data collected until then.

**SaleCycle**

**www.salecycle.com**

It collects information about your use of the website to understand what products and services are of interest to you and a set of personal data such as your name, email address, phone number and a unique identifier associated with your device. This information may be used to assist you in the purchase process by contacting you occasionally (by email or SMS) or to customize the advertising you view online. Please read the SaleCycle Services Privacy Policy for more details on the navigation data used by SaleCycle on our behalf.

**Cookie Policy Extended Information**

Michele Franzese Moda reserves the right personal data, voluntarily provided by Users, in compliance with current regulations. Users are invited to periodically visit this section in order to be updated on changes related in current legislation.

**What are cookies?**

Cookies are small text files sent from the site to the user's terminal ( usually to the browser ), where they are stored before being re-transmitted to the site at the next visit by the same user. A cookie can not retrieve any other data from the user's hard disk nor transmit computer viruses or acquire email addresses. Each cookie is unique to the user's web browser. Some of the function of cookies can be delegated to other technologies. In this document, the term "cookie" refers to both cookies, properly so-called, and to all similar technologies.

**Type of cookies and purposes**

Michele Franzese Moda uses different types of cookies and reltaed technologies, each of which has a specific function: technical and profiling cookies. Technical cookies are necessary for the proper functioning of the site and allow you to view the contents on the device by recognizing the language and market from which the users has chosen to connect. If the user is registered, they allow access to the services offered and to recognized the visitor to subsequent access. Profiling cookies improves the quality and the browsing experience.

**Cookies installed on the website**

Here's the list of cookies on the site. Third party cookies have the link to the privacy policy of the relative external supplier, where it is possible to find a detailed description of the individual cookies and of the treatment that is made of them.

**List of technical cookies on the website**

System cookies

Michele Franzese Moda uses cookies to guarantee a better browsing experience; these cookies are essential for the correct use of the site. You can disable these cookies from the browser by following the instructions in the dedicated paragraph, but you will compromise your experience on the website and we will not be able to respond to malfunctions.

**Facebook**

Facebook uses cookies to provide the user with sharing and "like" features on their personal wall. For more information, see the page [https://www.facebook.com/about/privacy ](https://www.facebook.com/about/privacy)

**Google Analytics**

These are tracking cookies for generating statistics on the use of the site. Google Analytics uses cookies that do not store personal data and are stored on the user's computer to allow the website operator to analyze how users use the site. To prevent the storage of the aforementioned cookies, the user can follow the procedure available at the following link: [ _https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=it_](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=it)

**Twitter**

Twitter uses cookies to provide the user with sharing funcionality on their wall.

For more information, see the pages: [https://support.twitter.com/articles/20170519-uso-dei-cookie-e-di- altre-tecnologie-simili-da-parte-di-twitter](https://support.twitter.com/articles/20170519-uso-dei-cookie-e-di-altre-tecnologie-simili-da-parte-di-twitter) and [https://twitter.com/privacy?lang=it](https://twitter.com/privacy?lang=it)

**List of profiling cookies on the site**

**Google Adwords Remarketing**

Google Adwords Remarketing installs cookies to study and improve advertising, with remarketing actions, in order to send to the user, messages in line with their interests. Remarketing helps you reach users who have visited the site. Previous visitors or users can see site ads as they browse websites that appear on the Google Display Network or search for terms related to our products on Google. More information, also in relation to the ways you can disable these cookies, can be seen at this link: <https://support.google.com/adwords/answer/2407785?hl=it>   

To select/deselect the cookie click here [http://www.google.com/settings/ads](http://www.google.com/settings/ads)

**Facebook Pixel**

Facebook installs cookies to study and improve advertising, with remarketing actions, in order to send to users messages in line with their interests.Remarketing helps to reach users who have visited the site. 

More information, also in relation to the ways in which these cookies can be disabled, can be found at this link: [https://www.facebook.com/policies/cookies/](https://www.facebook.com/policies/cookies/)

**SaleCycle  Cookie**

<https://www.salecycle.com/cookie-policy/>  

**Cookie management**

In compliance with the directives of the Code regarding the protection of personal data ( legislative decree of 30 June 2003, n° 196, hereinafter referred to as the "Code") and, in particular, with articles 13, paragraph 3 and 122, subsection 1 and with reference to the provision of identification of the simplified procedures for the information and the acquisition of consent ofr the use of cookies - 8 May 2014 ( Published on the Official Gazette N° 126 of 3 June 2014), you can change consent to cookies at any time by reading the next section "How to disable / delete cookies" .

LuxuryOfLove S.R.L. take appropriate trace of the User's consent(s) through a specific technical cookie, considered by the Data Protection Authority as a "not particularly invasive" tool. The User can deny his consent and/or modify at anytime his own options regarding the use of cookies by this Website, by accessing this Privacy Notice which is linkable from each page of this website. 

The User has the faculty at any time to exercise the rights recognized by the art. 7 of Legislative Decree 196/2003 and, in particular, among others, to obtain a copy of the processed data, their updating, their origin, the purpose and the mode of treatment, their rectification or integration, their cancellation, the transformation into an anonymous form or the block for the processing in violation of the law and to oppose the processing for legitimate reasons. 

To exercise these rights, write to privacy@franzesemoda.it to the attention of the Marketing and Communication Area, or contact us thorugh our website.

If you want to change the permissions of cookies, you must delete them through the browser, as shown below, because otherwise those already installed will not be removed. In particular, please note that it is not possible in any way to control third-party cookies, so if the consent has already been given, it is necessary to delete cookies through the browser (dedicated section) or by asking for the opt-out directly to third parties or via <http://www.youronlinechoices.com/it/le-tue-scelte>  

If you want to know more, you can consult the following sites:

• [http://www.youronlinechoices.com/](http://www.youronlinechoices.com/)  
• [http://www.allaboutcookies.org/](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/)   
• [https://www.cookiechoices.org/](https://www.cookiechoices.org/)  
• [http://www.garanteprivacy.it/web/guest/home/docweb/-/docweb- display/docweb/3118884](http://www.garanteprivacy.it/web/guest/home/docweb/-/docweb-display/docweb/3118884)

**How to disable/delete cookies by configuring the browser**

We remind you that disabling cookies or navigation functional ones can cause the site to malfunction and/or limit the service we offer.

**Chrome**

1\. Run Chrome browser

2\. Click on the menu in the browser toolbar next to the url input window for navigation

3\. Select **Setting** **s**

4\. Click **Show Advanced Settings**

5\. In the "Privacy" section click on the " **Content settings** " button

6\. In the "Cookies" section you can change the following cookie settings :

\- Allow data to be saved locally 

\- Change local data only until the browser is closed

\- Prevent sites from setting cookies

\- block third party cookies and site data

\- Manage exceptions for some websites

\- Delete one or all cookies 

For more information visit the [dedicated page](https://support.microsoft.com/it-it/help/17442/windows-internet-explorer-delete-manage-cookies).

**Mozilla Firefox**

1\. Run the Mozilla Firefox browser

2. Click on the menu in the browser toolbar next to the url input window for navigation

3\. Select **Settings**

4. ** ** Select **Privacy** panel

5\. Click on **Show Advanced Settings**

6. ** ** In the " **Privacy** " section click on " **Contents Settings** " button

7\. In the "Tracking" section you can change the following cookies settings:

\- Ask the sites not to make any tracking

\- Notify sites the availability to be tracked

\- Do not communicate any preference regarding the tracking of personal data

8\. From the " **History** " section you can:

\- Enabling "Use custom settings" select to accept third-party cookies ( always, from most visited sites or never) and to store them for a specified period (until their expiration, when Firefox closes or ask every time)

\- Remove individual cookies stored. 

For more information visit the [dedicated page](https://support.mozilla.org/en-US/kb/enable-and-disable-cookies-website-preferences).

**Internet Explorer**

1\. Run the Internet Explorer browser

2\. Click the **Tools** button and select **Internet Options**

3\. Click on the **Privacy** tab and, in the **Settings** section, change the slider according to the desired action for cookies:

- Black all cookies

\- Allow all cookies 

\- Select the sites from which to obtain cookies: move the cursor to an intermediate position so as not to block or allow all cookies, then click on Sites, in the Website Address box enter a website and then click on Block or Allow.

For more information visit the [dedicated page](https://support.microsoft.com/it-it/help/17442/windows-internet-explorer-delete-manage-cookies). 

**Safari 6**

1\. Run Safari browser

2\. Click on **Safari** , select **Preference** and click on **Privacy**

3\. In the Block Cookies section, specify how Safari must accept cookies from websites.

4\. To view which sites have stored cookies click on **Details**

For more information visit the dedicated page.

**Safari IOS** (mobile devices)

1\. Run Safari iOS browser

2\. Tap on **Settings** and then **Safari**

3\. Tap on **Block Cookies  **and choose from the various options: "Never", "Third Party and advertisers" or "Always".

4\. To delete all cookies stored by Safari, tap on **Settings** , then on Safari and then on Delete Cookies and data.

For more information, visit the [dedicated page](https://support.apple.com/en-us/HT201265)

**Opera**

1\. Run Opera Browser

2\. Click on **Preferences**  then on Advanced and finally on Cookies

3\. Select one of the following options:

\- Accept all cookies

\- Accept cookies only from the site you visit: third party cookies and those that are sent from a domain other than the one you are visiting will be rejected.

\- Never accept cookies: all cookies will never be saved. For more information visit the [dedicated page](https://www.opera.com/help/tutorials/security/privacy/)

Privacy policy updated on 28/05/2018

TIMETABLES:

Monday - Friday: 11:00 \- 13:30 and 16:00 - 18:00

Saturday: 11.00 \- 13.30

Information Email: info@michelefranzesemoda.com

Returns, Payments and bank transfer copies: eshop@michelefranzesemoda.com

Whatsapp Customer Care: +39 3938751105

Tel: 081 5306493

TIMETABLES:

Monday - Friday: 9.00 - 18.00

Saturday: 9.00 - 13.30

Via Antonio D'auria 32 Sant'Anastasia 80048

Tel: 081 5306493

Timetables:

Monday - 10.00-13.30 / 16.00 - 20.30

Tuesday - Saturday : 10.00 \- 13.30, 16.00 - 20.30

Via Domenico Morelli 6/8/10 B angolo Piazza dei Martiri

Tel: 081 5303983

Monday - 16.00 - 20.30

Tuesday - Saturday : 9.00 \- 13.30, 16.00 - 20.30

Via Antonio D'auria 32-34 Sant'Anastasia 80048

Mobile: 081 5303983

**Michele Franzese Moda** offers its Customers various payment methods:

Credit Cards

Paypal

MyBank

Alipay

Unionpay

Sofort

Wechat

The financial information of Customers making purchases on the Michele Franzese Moda website (credit card number, credit card expiry date and other personal information) will be processed exclusively by Banca Sella and will never be in the possession of or disclosed to **Michele Franzese Moda**

**PAYMENT BY CREDIT CARD**

The **Michele Franzese Moda** website accepts Visa, Mastercard, Circuito Gest Pay, Maestro, American Express e Bancomat,  Diners, JCB Cards, Hype,  My Bank, Tim Personal, Sofort Banking, Master Pass credit cards and uses the currently most secure methods, with the additional guarantee provided by the Mastercard Securecode and Verified by VISA services. 

**PAYMENTS BY PAYPAL**

Customers may pay for purchases by a verified Paypal account according to the methods established by PayPal, which account holders should be familiar with. Michelefranzesemoda reserves the right to process orders only if shipped to the same address that the verified PayPal account is registered with.

GENERAL CONDITIONS OF SALE

General conditions of Sale  
The products purchased on Michele Franzese Moda are sold directly by LuxuryofLove srl an Italian company, with registered office in Via Montenapoleone, 8 – 20121 Milano, registered at the Chamber of Commerce No. REA  MI-2550891  
The offer and sale of products on the website Michele Franzese Moda are governed by these Terms of Sale.  
The General Conditions of Sale can be periodically updated; They are considered effective and binding those published on Michele Franzese Moda   accepted at check out.  
Please read carefully the terms and conditions of sale before purchasing.  
How to purchase  
For each selected product displays a description page, with a picture and the essential characteristics, for example: the color, the size, the unit price.  
The images and colors of products offered for sale to Michele Franzese Moda   may not match the actual ones due to the Internet browser and / or monitor Michele Franzese Moda   is not liable for any inaccuracies due to a particular configuration of the computer or its malfunction.  
Product Availability  
The products offered for sale and their prices are those on the Michele Franzese Moda

Customers can order a maximun of 1 quantity of any item with the *ICON tag. In the case of the customer do not follow this rule, michelefranzesemoda.com takes the right to cancel the order and refund the customer.

Items tagged as *ICON in the detailed description, are excluded from any promotion or coupon

During free shipping promotions, we will not accept orders under 100 Euro

If, at the time of the order, the products are not available the relevant size is not displayed.  
If, due to the simultaneous purchase by individual customers, the product ordered is no longer available, it is sent an e-mail to cancel the order.  
Michele Franzese Moda   may change at any time and without notice the products offered for sale to Michele Franzese Moda and their prices.  
Product price  
The price of each item is indicated in Euro, Hong Kong dollar, Japanese Yen, Chinese Yuan, Pound  
The cost of shipping is displayed before payment.

The FTA invoice ( Free Trade Agreement ) can be issued only for orders receive from South Korea, which are less than 6,000 Euro and the items inside the package are of European origin

ORDER

Order  
The execution of the purchase order implies knowledge of these general conditions of sale and their unconditional acceptance.  
Orders can be placed upon registration and / or setting up an account ("register for free"). Remember to check out the Rules on Privacy and Terms and Conditions of Sale.  
The orders are compiled following the steps and instructions specified on the website.  
The purchase of the products offered for sale to Michele Franzese Moda   can be made by consumers / customers who have come of age and acting exclusively on their behalf.  
The sale and / or distribution of the products purchased on Michele Franzese Moda is prohibited.  
 Michele Franzese Moda . It reserves the right to consider the acceptance of orders received.  
Michele Franzese Moda   will notify the customer by e-mail of a possible failure to accept orders received.  
Order Confirmation  
The customer receives at the time of conclusion of the purchase written confirmation of the ordered product, the amount to be paid, with the detail of the product price and shipping.  
Payment methods  
Michele Franzese Moda. accepts the following payment methods:  
Bank Transfer  
Credit cards (including prepaid, postpaid)  
Michele Franzese Moda accepts payments with the following credit cards and debit cards: Visa, MasterCard, American Express, Master.

Any other payment formulas can be accepted only at the discretion of Michele Franzese Moda .For more information and / or assistance, you can send an email Michele Franzese Moda ordered products remain the property of Michele Franzese Moda until full collection of the relevant price.

Delivery area  
The delivery of products is made to the address required by the customer. We do not ship to PO Boxes.

Contacts:

**Registered Office** :  **LuxuryOfLove S.R.L. Via Montenapoleone 8 , 20121 Milano**

**Administrative Headquarters:  ** **Via Antonio D'Auria 32 Sant'Anastasia 80048 ( NA )**

**Telephone: 081 5306493**

DHL EXPRESS NETWORK TERMS AND CONDITIONS OF CARRIAGE AND CUSTOMS OPERATIONS (“T&C”)

These T&C are applied to services provided by Express Carrier DHL Express in respect of delivery of Express Shipments for personal use.

1\. Terms used herein:  
Express Carrier: DHL Express is represented within the Russian Federation by two entities, DHL International AO and DHL Express OOO.  DHL Express as well as third parties work together to deliver Express Shipments internationally and perform customs operations in respect of Express Shipments.  
Customs Broker means DHL Express OOO performing customs operations in the name and on behalf of the customs applicant and other interested parties in accordance with the customs laws of the Customs Union.  
Express Shipment means goods shipped in express mode by any means of transportation using electronic shipment organisation and tracking system on www.dhl.ru website to deliver those goods to the Consignee pursuant to an individual waybill within the shortest possible and/or fixed period of time.  
Shipper means a legal entity, normally an online store, that handed Express Shipments over to the Express Carrier for delivery.  
Consignee means an individual consignee of Express Shipment specified in the DHL Express waybill.

2\. T&C Subject Matter  
2.1. These T&C are a public offer and form a consensual type Delivery and Customs Operations Agreement in respect of Express Shipments by and between the Shipper/Consignee, the Express Carrier and the Customs Broker (“Agreement”).  
2.2. Consignee of Express Shipments accepts the provisions of this Agreement for themselves and for other directly or indirectly interested parties, including the Shipper, by pressing a button, ticking a box or putting any other sign in the box “I accept terms and conditions of the Public Offer,” as well as/or by any other means of actual confirmation of their consent when ordering goods at the Shipper’s website.  
2.3. Under the applicable legislation in Russian Federation Express Carrier and Customs Broker shall have the right to demand from Consignee documents and information necessary for international delivery of Express Shipments and customs operations in respect of Express Shipment, including those containing information comprising commercial, bank and other secrets protected by law, or other confidential information, and obtain such documents and information within the time limits ensuring observance of the requirements specified in the applicable legislation.  
Express Carrier and Customs Broker hereby acknowledge and confirm that the obtained information comprising state, commercial, bank and other secrets protected by the law or other confidential information must not be disclosed or used by Express Carrier and Customs Broker and their employees for their own purposes, handed over to other persons, except for the cases envisaged in the applicable legislation in Russian Federation other cases when disclose of the information is required for international delivery of Express Shipments and customs operations in respect of Express Shipment. 

3\. DHL Express Network Terms and Conditions of Carriage.  
3.1. The Shipper and the Consignee acknowledge that normal DHL Express Delivery Terms and Conditions apply to carriage of goods via DHL Express network; the key provisions thereof that are essential for the Consignee are listed below:  
Deliveries and Undeliverables  
Shipments cannot be delivered to PO Boxes or postal codes. Shipments are delivered to the Receiver’s address given by Shipper but not necessarily to the named Receiver personally. Shipments to addresses with a central receiving area will be delivered to that area.   
DHL may notify Receiver of an upcoming delivery or a missed delivery. Receiver may be offered alternative delivery options such as delivery on another day, no signature required, redirection or collection at a DHL Service Point. Shipper may exclude certain delivery options on request.  
If the Shipment is deemed to be unacceptable as described in Section 2, or it has been undervalued for customs purposes, or Receiver cannot be reasonably identified or located, or Receiver refuses delivery or to pay Customs Duties or other Shipment charges, DHL shall use reasonable efforts to return the Shipment to Shipper at Shipper’s cost, failing which the Shipment may be released, disposed of or sold without incurring any liability whatsoever to Shipper or anyone else, with the proceeds applied against Customs Duties, Shipment charges and related administrative costs with the balance of the proceeds of a sale to be returned to Shipper. DHL shall have the right to destroy any Shipment which any law prevents DHL from returning to Shipper as well as any Shipment of Dangerous Goods.  
Inspection  
DHL has the right to open and inspect a Shipment without notice for safety, security, customs or other regulatory reasons.   
DHL’s Liability  
DHL’s liability in respect of any one Shipment transported by air (including ancillary road transport or stops en route) is limited by the Montreal Convention or the Warsaw Convention, as applicable, or in absence of such Convention, to the lower of (i) the current market or declared value, or (ii) 19 Special Drawing Rights per kilogram (approximately $US 26.00 per kilogram). Such limits shall also apply to all other forms of transportation, except where Shipments are carried only by road, when the limits below apply.  
For cross border Shipments transported by road, DHL’s liability is or shall be deemed to be limited by the Convention for the International Carriage of Goods by Road (CMR) to the lower of (i) current market value or declared value, or (ii) 8.33 Special Drawing Rights per kilogram (approximately $US 14.00 per kilogram). Such limits will also apply to national road transportation in the absence of any mandatory or lower liability limits in the applicable national transport law.   
If Shipper regards these limits as insufficient it must make a special declaration of value and request insurance as described in Section 8 or make its own insurance arrangements.   
DHL’s liability is strictly limited to direct loss and damage to a Shipment only and to the per kilogram limits in this Section 6. All other types of loss or damage are excluded (including but not limited to lost profits, income, interest, future business), whether such loss or damage is special or indirect, and even if the risk of such loss or damage was brought to DHL’s attention.  
DHL will make every reasonable effort to deliver the Shipment according to DHL’s regular delivery schedules, but these schedules are not binding and do not form part of the contract. DHL is not liable for any damages or loss caused by delay, but for certain Shipments, Shipper may be able to claim limited delay compensation under the Money Back Guarantee terms and conditions, which are available on the DHL website at www.dhl.com or from Customer service.  
Claims  
All claims must be submitted in writing to DHL within thirty (30) days from the date that DHL accepted the Shipment, failing which DHL shall have no liability whatsoever. Claims are limited to one claim per Shipment, settlement of which will be full and final settlement for all loss or damage in connection therewith.  
Circumstances Beyond DHL’s Control  
DHL is not liable for any loss or damage arising out of circumstances beyond DHL’s control. These include but are not limited to electrical or magnetic damage to, or erasure of, electronic or photographic images, data or recordings; any defect or characteristic related to the nature of the Shipment, even if known to DHL; any act or omission by a person not employed or contracted by DHL - e.g. Shipper, Receiver, third party, customs or other government official; “Force Majeure” - e.g. earthquake, cyclone, storm, flood, fog, war, plane crash, embargo, riot, civil commotion, or industrial action.  
Routing  
Shipper agrees to all routing and diversion, including the possibility that the Shipment may be carried via intermediate stopping places.  
3.2 Full text of the текст DHL Express Network Terms and Conditions of Carriage is available on www.dhl.ru website.

4\. Customs Operations Terms & Conditions  
4.1. Customs Broker:  
4.1.1 may performs customs declaration of Express Shipments;  
4.1.2. shall inform the Consignee of the date of the goods arrival to the temporary storage facility (TSF) by fax or email;  
4.1.3. shall perform other actions stipulated in the customs laws of the Customs Union and the Russian Federation as necessary to perform the customs operations as a person authorized by the Consignee to act in respect of the declared Express Shipments.  
4.2. The Consignee shall provide comprehensive and accurate details and documents to perform declaration of the Express Shipments as stipulated in the customs laws of the Customs Union and the Russian Federation and provide additional documents at the Customs Broker’s request.  
All the documents required to declare the goods should be provided within ten (10) calendar days from the moment the goods arrive to the TSF.  
4.3.The Consignee would take of formalities related to the frequency of receiving shipments at his own risk and cost  
4.4.The Shipper and the Consignee guarantee that they have legal authority or other legal grounds for the Customs Broker to perform legally relevant actions on their behalf and shall be fully liable for providing comprehensive and accurate information in respect of the Express Shipments.

5\. Liability of the Parties  
5.1. The Consignee shall be liable for penal sanctions imposed on the Customs Broker as a result of the latter’s breach of customs regulations due to the Consignee’s failure to provide comprehensive and/or accurate information and documents, including inconsistencies in transported goods to their accompanying documents in terms of their name, quantity, other characteristics affecting due declaration, as well as the Consignee being late in providing those documents and information; and in that case the Consignee shall reimburse the Customs Broker all the amounts of such sanctions against a separate invoice.   
5.2. The Customs Broker shall not be liable for lost profits or other consequential and contingent damages of the Consignee even if such damages are foreseeable or have been made known to the Customs Broker or the Customs Broker could or should have known about them.  
5.3. The Parties shall be released from liability for full or partial non-performance of their respective obligations hereunder if it became a result of Force Majeure circumstances and those circumstances directly affected performance of this Agreement.

6\. Service Fees and Payment for Customs Operations:  
6.1. Service fees are determined based on the Customs Broker’s rates as of the invoice date, including amounts of customs and other fees paid by the Customs Broker while providing services hereunder.   
6.2. The Consignee must pay for the Customs Broker’s services.  
6.3. The Customs Broker reserves the right to withhold any goods of the Consignee at the latter’s expense until the Customer Broker’s services provided to the Consignee hereunder are paid in full.

7\. General Provisions  
7.1. Should the T&C and/or Agreement text change, the Parties agree to apply the T&C effective as of the date of consent specified in Clause 2.2.

УСЛОВИЯ ДОСТАВКИ И СОВЕРШЕНИЯ ТАМОЖЕННЫХ ОПЕРАЦИЙ  
ПО СЕТИ ЭКСПРЕСС-ПЕРЕВОЗЧИКА DHL EXPRESS (далее - Условия)

Настоящие Условия используются при оказании услуг Экспресс-перевозчиком DHL Express при доставке Экспресс-грузов для личного пользования.

1\. Термины, используемые в настоящих Условиях:  
Экспресс-перевозчик - DHL Express представлен на территории РФ двумя лицами: АО «ДХЛ Интернешнл» и ООО «ДХЛ Экспресс». DHL Express, а также третьи лица, осуществляют совместную деятельность по международной перевозке Экспресс-грузов и совершению таможенных операций в отношении Экспрес-грузов.  
Таможенный представитель – ООО «ДХЛ Экспресс», совершающее от имени и по поручению декларанта или иных заинтересованных лиц таможенные операции в соответствии с таможенным законодательством Таможенного Союза.  
Экспресс-груз – товар, перевозимый в рамках скоростной перевозки любыми видами транспорта с использованием электронной информационной системы организации и отслеживания перевозок на сайте www.dhl.ru в целях доставки данного товара до Получателя в соответствии с индивидуальной транспортной накладной в течение минимально возможного и/или фиксированного промежутка времени.  
Отправитель – юридическое лицо, обычно интернет-магазин, передавшее Экспресс-перевозчику Экспресс-груз для доставки.  
Получатель – физическое лицо, получатель Экспресс-груза, указанный на транспортной накладной DHL Express.

2\. Предмет настоящих Условий  
2.1. Настоящие Условия представляют собой публичную оферту и составляют Договор перевозки и совершения таможенных операций в отношении Экспресс-грузов консенсуального типа, совершаемый между Отправителем/Получателем, Экспресс-перевозчиком и Таможенным представителем (далее - Договор).  
2.2. Нажатием кнопки, проставлением галочки либо другого знака в поле «Я принимаю условия Публичной оферты» а также/либо какого-либо другого фактического подтверждения согласия на сайте Отправителя при заказе Получатель Экспресс-грузов принимает положения настоящего Договора от своего имени и от имени иных прямо или косвенно заинтересованных лиц, включая и Отправителя.  
2.3. В соответствии с применимым в РФ законодательством Экспресс-перевозчик и Таможенный представитель вправе требовать от Получателя документы и сведения, необходимые для выполнения международной перевозки Экспресс-грузов и совершению таможенных операций в отношении Экспресс-грузов, в том числе содержащие информацию, составляющую коммерческую, банковскую и иную охраняемую законом тайну, либо другую конфиденциальную информацию, и получать такие документы и сведения в сроки, обеспечивающие соблюдение установленных законодательством требований. Экспресс-перевозчик и Таможенный представитель признает и подтверждает, что полученная информация, составляющая государственную, коммерческую, банковскую и иную охраняемую законом тайну (секреты), либо другая конфиденциальная информация не будет разглашаться или использоваться Экспресс-перевозчиком, Таможенным представителем и их работниками для собственных целей, передаваться иным лицам, за исключением случаев, предусмотренных законодательством, применимым в РФ, а также случаев, когда передача информации иным лицом необходима для выполнения международной перевозки Экспресс-грузов и совершения таможенных операций в отношении Экспресс-грузов.

3\. Условия доставки по сети DHL Express.  
3.1. Отправитель и Получатель согласны с тем, что для транспортировки грузов по сети DHL Express применяются обычные Условия доставки DHL Express, основные положения которых, важные для Получателя, перечислены ниже:  
Доставка и невозможность доставки  
Грузы не могут быть доставлены по адресам абонентских ящиков или с указанием только почтовых индексов. Грузы доставляются по адресу Грузополучателя, указанному Грузоотправителем, однако, не обязательно лично Грузополучателю. Доставка Грузов, адресованных в центральную зону получения грузов, производится именно в эту зону.   
«DHL» может уведомить Грузополучателя о предстоящей доставке или пропуске доставки. Грузополучателю могут быть предложены альтернативные варианты доставки, в том числе доставка в другой день, доставка без подписи, перенаправление по другому адресу или самовывоз из сервисного отделения «DHL». Некоторые варианты доставки могут быть исключены по требованию Грузоотправителя.  
В случае неприемлемости груза, как указано в ст. 2, его заниженной таможенной стоимости, невозможности нахождения или идентификации Грузополучателя с помощью разумных мер, отказа Грузополучателя от доставки или оплаты Таможенных пошлин или иных связанных с Грузом сборов «DHL» предпримет все зависящие от него меры для возврата Груза Грузоотправителю за счет последнего; в противном случае Груз поступает в распоряжение «DHL» и может быть выдан, отчужден или реализован по его усмотрению без какой-либо ответственности перед Грузоотправителем и любыми иными лицами, а вырученные от реализации денежные средства за вычетом Таможенных пошлин, связанных с Грузом сборов и соответствующих административных расходов подлежат возврату Грузоотправителю. «DHL» вправе уничтожить любой Груз, который «DHL» не может вернуть Грузоотправителю в силу закона, а также любой Груз, содержаний Опасные грузы во вложении.  
Инспектирование  
«DHL» имеет право вскрывать и инспектировать Грузы без уведомления в целях обеспечения безопасности, таможенного декларирования или в соответствии с иными регламентирующими и нормативными актами.  
Ответственность «DHL»  
Ответственность «DHL» в отношении любого Груза, перевозка которого осуществляется авиационным транспортом (включая вспомогательную перевозку автотранспортом или остановки на маршруте) ограничена в соответствии с Монреальской или Варшавской конвенциями, или, при неприменимости указанных конвенций -   меньшей из следующих сумм: (i) текущая рыночная или объявленная стоимость или (ii) 19 специальных прав заимствования за килограмм (приблизительно 26,00 долл.США за килограмм). Такие ограничения также применяются ко всем иным видам грузоперевозок, с тем исключением, что в случае перевозки Грузов автомобильным транспортом действуют ограничения, перечисленные ниже.  
В случае международной перевозки Грузов автомобильным транспортом ответственность «DHL» ограничивается или считается ограниченной условиями Конвенции о договоре международной перевозки грузов автомобильным транспортом (КДПГ) в размере меньшей из следующих сумм: (i) текущая рыночная или объявленная стоимость или (ii) 8,33 специальных прав заимствования за килограмм (приблизительно 14,00 долл.США за килограмм). В отсутствие подлежащих применению в силу закона  или более низких ограничений ответственности в действующем национальном законодательстве такие ограничения также применяются к внутренней перевозке грузов автомобильным транспортом.  
Если Грузоотправитель сочтет вышеприведенные предельные суммы выплат недостаточными, он должен отдельно объявить ценность груза и заявить о необходимости его страхования в соответствии с положениями Раздела 8 (Страхование Грузов), либо самостоятельно застраховать Груз.  
Размер ответственности «DHL» однозначно ограничивается непосредственным реальным ущербом, причиненным Грузу в результате его повреждения либо утраты, и не может превышать предельных значений в расчете на килограмм веса Груза согласно настоящему Разделу  6\. Не подлежат возмещению любые иные виды убытков или ущерба, (включая, помимо прочего, упущенную выгоду, процентный доход и деловую перспективу), вне зависимости от того, является ли подобный ущерб и убытки особыми или косвенными, даже в том случае, если «DHL» было поставлено в известность о риске возникновения подобного ущерба или убытков.  
 «DHL» обязуется приложить все разумные усилия для доставки Груза согласно обычному графику доставки «DHL», однако такой график не является обязательным и не входит в состав договора. «DHL» не несет ответственности за ущерб или убытки, вызванные задержкой, однако в случае определенных Грузов Грузоотправитель вправе потребовать ограниченную компенсацию за задержку согласно условиям Гарантии возврата денег, с которыми можно ознакомиться на интернет сайте «DHL»  по адресу www.dhl.com или обратившись в DHL.  
Срок предъявления претензий  
Все претензии должны быть заявлены «DHL» в письменном виде в течение 30 (тридцати) дней с момента приема груза «DHL»; в противном случае «DHL» не будет нести по претензиям никакой ответственности. В отношении одного Груза можно заявить только одну претензию, при этом ее урегулирование является полным и окончательным урегулированием всех требований о возмещении ущерба и убытков в отношении такого Груза.  
 Независящие от «DHL» обстоятельства  
«DHL» не несет ответственность за какой-либо ущерб и убытки, вызванные не зависящими от «DHL» обстоятельствами. Указанные обстоятельства, помимо прочего, включают: негативное воздействие электрических или магнитных полей на электронные или фотографические изображения, данные или записи или их стирание, любые дефекты или характеристики, обусловленные характером Груза, даже если о них было сообщено «DHL»; любые действия или бездействие лиц, не являющихся сотрудниками или подрядчиками «DHL», а именно, Грузоотправителя, Грузополучателя, третьей стороны, таможенных органов или иных официальных лиц; «Форс-мажорные обстоятельства» — землетрясение, циклон, ураган, наводнение, туман, военные действия, катастрофа воздушного судна, эмбарго, мятеж, массовые беспорядки или производственные конфликты.   
Маршрут следования  
Грузоотправитель соглашается с любым маршрутом следования и отклонениями от него, включая возможность прохождения Груза через промежуточные перевалочные пункты.  
Применимое законодательство  
Любые споры, возникающие из настоящих Условий, или в связи с ними, в интересах «DHL» подлежат рассмотрению в судах страны отправления Груза и регулируются законодательством этой страны, при этом Грузоотправитель обязуется признать указанную юрисдикцию, если это не противоречит действующему законодательству.  
3.2 Полный текст Условий доставки по сети DHL Express доступен на сайте www.dhl.ru .

4\. Условия совершения таможенных операций  
4.1. Таможенный представитель:  
4.1.1 вправе производить таможенное декларирование Экспресс-груза;  
4.1.2 обязуется информировать Получателя о дате прибытия товаров на склад временного хранения (далее – СВХ) посредством факсимильной или электронной связи;  
4.1.3 обязуется совершать другие действия, предусмотренные таможенным законодательством Таможенного Союза и Российской Федерации, необходимые для совершения таможенных операций, в качестве лица, наделенного Получателем полномочиями в отношении декларируемых Экспресс-грузов.  
4.2. Получатель обязуется предоставлять Таможенному представителю полные и достоверные сведения и документы, предусмотренные таможенным законодательством Таможенного Союза и Российской Федерации, для осуществления декларирования Экспресс-грузов, а также в соответствии с запросом Таможенного представителя представлять дополнительные документы.  
Все необходимые документы для декларирования товаров должны быть представлены не позднее 10 (десять) календарных дней с момента прибытия товаров на склад временного хранения  
4.3. Получатель обязуется самостоятельно соблюдать все формальности, связанные с частотой перемещения им грузов через таможенную границу.  
4.4.Отправитель и Получатель гарантируют юридические правомочия или иные законные основания на совершение юридически значимых действий Таможенного представителя от их имени и несут полную ответственность за предоставление полной и достоверной информации относительно Экспресс груза.

5\. Ответственность Сторон  
5.1. Получатель несет ответственность за штрафные санкции, наложенные на Таможенного представителя вследствие нарушения последним таможенных правил в связи с предоставлением Получателем неполной и/или недостоверной информации и документов, в том числе, несоответствия перевозимых товаров сопроводительным документам в части их наименования, количества, иных характеристик, влияющих на достоверное декларирование, а равно несвоевременного предоставления Получателем указанных документов и информации, и в этом случае Получатель обязуется возместить Таможенному представителю суммы таких санкций на основании отдельного счета.   
5.2. Таможенный представитель не несет ответственность за упущенную выгоду, а также иные косвенные и непредвиденные убытки Получателя, даже если такие убытки предсказуемы или если Таможенный представитель был о них уведомлен, или мог бы или должен бы был знать о них.  
5.3. Стороны освобождаются от ответственности за частичное или полное неисполнение обязательств по настоящему Договору, если оно явилось следствием обстоятельств непреодолимой силы, и если эти обстоятельства непосредственно повлияли на исполнение данного Договора.

6\. Тарифы и оплата услуг по совершению таможенных операций:  
6.1. Стоимость услуг определяется в соответствии с тарифами Таможенного представителя на дату выставления счета, включая суммы таможенных и иных платежей, уплаченных Таможенным представителем при оказании услуг по настоящему Договору.   
6.2. Услуги Таможенного представителя должны быть оплачены Получателем.  
6.3. Таможенный представитель оставляет за собой право за счет Получателя удерживать любые товары последнего до момента получения Таможенным представителем полной оплаты услуг, оказанных Получателю по настоящему Договору.

7\. Общие положения  
7.1. В случае изменения текста Условий и/или Договора, Стороны соглашаются, что будут применены Условия, действующие на дату получения согласия, указанного в п. 2.2.

TERMS AND CONDITIONS

Buying from Michele Franzese Moda is simple and secure.  
The Customer should view the collections, choose the product and order it.  
The online store offers apparel and accessories from the top brands in international fashion.   
The exclusive service and unmistakable style of  Michele Franzese Moda _ ** **_ will make shopping a unique experience.  
To navigate through the product range, just select a CATEGORY and discover a selection of products from the leading Italian and international brands offered by _**Michele Franzese Moda**_.  
Each product is accompanied by a description which displays information on the model, price, style, sizes and colours.

By clicking on ADD TO CART, the desired item is placed in a virtual shopping bag, so you can continue to navigate through the other pages of the site until you confirm the order.  
New items may be added to the cart at any time, and previously selected items can be removed through the REMOVE ITEM function.

By clicking on the SHOPPING BAG link, you can view the prices of the individual items purchased and the total price of the order while it is still partial and unconfirmed.  
With the WISHLIST function, while shopping you can create a list of favourite items that will be saved in a separate area

              SHIPPING INFORMATION

**Michele Franzese Moda** ships in Italy and worldwide DHL & UPS express courier service.  
All merchandise sent by **Michele Franzese Moda** is carefully packaged.  
**Michele Franzese Moda** will ship the merchandise with the related invoice containing details on prices and discounts applied, also in the event of sale items.

FREE INSURANCE

All shipments by **Michele Franzese Moda** are covered by free insurance for theft and/or accidental damage.  
The insurance remains valid until the merchandise is delivered.

ORDER PROCESSING

All fully completed and paid orders will be processed within two business days: all shipments are sent from **Michele Franzese Moda** , only on business days, from Monday to Friday from 9:00 a.m. to 5:30 p.m.  
Orders entered on Saturdays and Sundays will be dealt with the next Tuesday.

ONLINE SHIPMENT TRACKING

**Michele Franzese Moda** customers can track their shipments at any time by using the DHL e UPS tracking service.  
The Customer will receive a merchandise shipment confirmation email with a DHL e UPS tracking number that can be used to check the shipment status at any time.  
Or, delivery status can always be  checked in real time in the “My Account” section of the website.

WORLDWIDE SHIPPING

Shipments may be DDP (Delivery Duty Pay) or DDU (Delivery Duty Unpaid), depending on the delivery address.  
DDP (Delivery Duty Pay) shipments are sent to EU countries (Austria, Belgium, Cyprus, Denmark, Estonia, Finland, France, Germany, Greece, Ireland, Italy, Latvia, Lithuania, Luxembourg, Malta, the Netherlands, Poland, Portugal, the United Kingdom, the Czech Republic, Slovakia, Slovenia, Spain, Sweden and Hungary), for which VAT is already calculated and included in the purchase price.  
DDU (Delivery Duty Unpaid) shipments are sent to non-EU or non-Schengen countries, which are not subject to VAT on the purchase price.

DELIVERY TIME

Delivery time depends on the destination of the products.  
ITALY (DDP): delivery is indicatively expected within 5/12 days of shipping.  
EU European Countries (DDP): delivery is indicatively expected within 3/5 business days of shipping.  
Non-EU European Countries (DDU): delivery is indicatively expected within 5/7 business days of shipping.  
Rest of the World: delivery is indicatively expected in up to 7-10 days after shipping by Express Service.

DELIVERY CONDITIONS

Once the merchandise has been delivered, the Customer is responsible for carefully inspecting the package before signing the delivery document.  
If the package has been tampered with or is not intact, the Customer may sign the delivery document subject to confirmation or refuse the delivery.  
Any irregularities must be promptly reported to the local DHL or UPS office and to Michele Franzese Moda, by sending an email to our customer service.  
If the Customer refuses to accept the merchandise, all shipping costs to return to package to **Michele Franzese Moda** will be deducted from the refund due to the Customer.  
If for any reason whatsoever the shipment is not delivered to the address provided by the Customer during registration, the package will be sent back to **Michele Franzese Moda** at the expense of the Customer.    
In this case, **Michele Franzese Moda** shall arrange to deduct that amount from any refund due to the Customer.

**Shipping fees are: 6  Euro in Italy, 15 Euro for European Countries and 30 Euro rest of the world**

**Michele Franzese Moda** ships in Italy and worldwide with the best courier services; **DHL and UPS**

All merchandise sent by **Michele Franzese Moda**  is carefully packaged.

**Michele Franzese Moda** will ship the merchandise with the related invoice containing details on prices and discounts applied, also in the event of sale items.

**FREE INSURANCE**

All shipments by **Michele Franzese Moda** are covered by free insurance for theft and/or accidental damage.  
The insurance remains valid until the merchandise is delivered.

**ORDER PROCESSING**

All fully completed and paid orders will be processed within two business days: all shipments are sent from **Michele Franzese Moda**., (Italy), only on business days, from Monday to Friday from 9:00 a.m. to 5:30 p.m.  
Orders entered on Saturdays and Sundays will be dealt with the next Tuesday.

**ONLINE SHIPMENT TRACKING**

**Michele Franzese Moda **customers can track their shipments at any time by using the DHL or UPS tracking service.  
The Customer will receive a merchandise shipment confirmation email with a DHL and UPS tracking number that can be used to check the shipment status at any time.

**https://www.ups.com/WebTracking/track?loc=en_us           Track with UPS**

**http://www.dhl.com/en/express/tracking/tracking_tools.html    Track with DHL**

**WORLDWIDE SHIPPING**

Shipments may be DDP (Delivery Duty Pay) or DDU (Delivery Duty Unpaid), depending on the delivery address.  
DDP (Delivery Duty Pay) shipments are sent to EU countries (Austria, Belgium, Cyprus, Denmark, Estonia, Finland, France, Germany, Greece, Ireland, Italy, Latvia, Lithuania, Luxembourg, Malta, the Netherlands, Poland, Portugal, the United Kingdom, the Czech Republic, Slovakia, Slovenia, Spain, Sweden and Hungary), for which VAT is already calculated and included in the purchase price.  
DDU (Delivery Duty Unpaid) shipments are sent to non-EU or non-Schengen countries, which are not subject to VAT on the purchase price.

**DELIVERY TIME**

Delivery time depends on the destination of the products.  
ITALY (DDP): delivery is indicatively expected within two business days from the shipping.  
EU European Countries (DDP): delivery is indicatively expected within three business days from the shipping.  
Rest of the World: delivery is indicatively expected in up to 4/5 business days. For orders made after the 10.00 AM (Italian time zone) they will be shipped on the next Monday. 

In sales time, the delivery may be subject to delay and will be processed within 72 working hours. There may be delays for major causes, such as adverse weather or custom checkings

**DELIVERY CONDITIONS**

Once the merchandise has been delivered, the Customer is responsible for carefully inspecting the package before signing the delivery document.  
If the package has been tampered with or is not intact, the Customer may sign the delivery document subject to confirmation or refuse the delivery.

Any irregularities must be promptly reported to the local DHL or UPS office and to **Michele Franzese Moda** , by sending an email to our customer service. In case of tampered package, if the customer does not sign the receipt with reserve, the shipment is considered automatically accepted and claims are not accepted.

If the Customer refuses to accept the merchandise, all shipping costs to return to package to **Michele Franzese Moda** will be deducted from the refund due to the Customer.  
If for any reason whatsoever the shipment is not delivered to the address provided by the Customer during registration, the package will be sent back to [ **nomesito]** at the expense of the Customer.    
In this case, **Michele Franzese Moda**  shall arrange to deduct that amount from any refund due to the Customer.

The shipping address and the State that customers write in the order, must be correct. Michele Franzese Moda have the right to cancel orders if customers write a differrent State despite the address given

Michele Franzese Moda takes to right to ask customers addional shipping fees for orders containing many items that could increase the weight or the numbers of the boxes, and consequently the shipping costs. The fee will be calculated using the DHL platform.

Collect points with our loyalty program. The more points you will earn, the more discounts you will receive by Michele Franzese Moda!

Specifically, for each euro spent, you will receive 1 MF point (Michele Franzese). Once you reach 1000 points, you can request a voucher worth € 100 up to a maximum limit of 5000 points for a value of € 500.

Remember to log in to your personal user area with your registration credentials to be eligible for the voucher.

For any queries, do not hesitate to contact us:

Start collecting points soon…
